formsite.com 2017-01-16

# Online Form Builder - Privacy Statement

Your privacy is important to us. Whether you are a Formsite customer or a form visitor, your information represents your trust in our organization and this page is intended to help you understand what we collect and what we do with it.

Information we collect

**Formsite customers**

When you sign up for a Formsite account, you give us some personal information like your email address. If you choose to pay for a service upgrade using a credit card, we collect your name, billing address, and credit card information. If you email us, your email address and any personal information is contained and archived.

We use commonly-used internet technologies like cookies and Google Analytics to track and analyze site visitors and customer interactions.

Your Formsite account activities and IP address are logged when you are logged-in to your account, as are many of your actions related to form building, results processing, and other services provided inside your account.

**Form visitors**

Formsite form visitors who complete forms made by our customers and may, depending entirely on the customers' forms, divulge personal information and/or manually uploaded files, are collected and stored within our secure database and file storage areas.

Form visitor logs are kept to track site usage, statistical information on technical capabilities and version numbers, and behavioral tracking.

How we use your information

**Formsite customers**

Formsite uses your information as part of your requested services as a Formsite user. We may use your information to improve our web site, services, and advertising.

Formsite may send you email messages on a regular basis to keep you apprised of your membership status and inform you of new services available to you. Included in each of these messages are simple instructions on how to remove yourself from these mailings if you do not wish to receive them in the future.

Formsite does not sell, share, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We may share information collected with third parties that work on our behalf for service improvement and analysis, or as may be required by law.

**Form visitors**

Formsite does not access, view, sell, share, rent, or trade any information collected by customer forms on any regular basis for any purposes aside from naturally occurring exposure as a result of customer support, fraud prevention, or other maintenance activities, or as may be required by law.

Privacy Shield

Formsite participates in and has certified that we adhere to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access, and Enforcement. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/ "Privacy Shield website").

Formsite's adherence to the Privacy Shield policies are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States Federal Trade Commission.

**Inquiries & Complaints**

All inquiries and complaints related to Privacy Shield are to be directed to our customer support staff at <https://www.formsite.com/contact.html> and will be replied to within 45 days.

For all unresolved complaints regarding Formsite's compliance with Privacy Shield, the independent recourse mechanism to escalate the matter is established as the United States Council for International Business (USCIB). For more information visit <https://www.uscib.org/>. The complaint form can be accessed directly at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/assistance>.

Your personal data

Customers of Formsite may view and modify their personal information from within their Formsite account. EU customers and form visitors have the right to access their personal data and to limit the use of their personal data.

Due to the nature of our service, EU form visitors requesting access to or limiting access to their personal information are required to provide the form link, notification email, and/or any other information needed to identify the Formsite account owner, at which time we will refer your request to that customer and will support them as needed to respond to your request.

Legal disclosure

Formsite may be required to disclose personal information to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
